<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="net.sf.caltrop.eclipse.plugin.calfeature"
      label="Caltrop Editor"
      version="1.0.6"
      provider-name="net.sf.caltrop">

   <description>
      CAL plug-in for Eclipse.
Latest Features:
* Problem marker tooltips now functional
* Fixes Eclipse shutdown issue
* Latest syntax fixes for NL and CAL.
Known Issues:
* most features unavailable when editing outside a project
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright (c) 2007, Xilinx Inc.
All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license>
      Copyright (c) 2007, Xilinx Inc.
All rights reserved.
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, 
with or without modification, are permitted provided 
that the following conditions are met:
- Redistributions of source code must retain the above 
copyright notice, this list of conditions and the 
following disclaimer.
- Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the 
above copyright notice, this list of conditions and 
the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or 
other materials provided with the distribution.
- Neither the name of Xilinx Inc. nor the names 
of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote 
products derived from this software without specific 
prior written permission.
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND 
CONTRIBUTORS &quot;AS IS&quot; AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, 
INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF 
MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE 
DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT OWNER OR 
CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT
NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES;
LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) 
HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN 
CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR
OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS 
SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="Caltrop Editor" url="http://caltrop.sourceforge.net/eclipse"/>
      <discovery label="Caltrop Site" url="http://caltrop.sourceforge.net"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface.text"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.editors"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.workbench.texteditor"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.views"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="net.sf.caltrop.eclipse.plugin.caldoc"
         download-size="485"
         install-size="485"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="net.sf.caltrop.eclipse.plugin.caleditor"
         download-size="4108"
         install-size="4108"
         version="0.0.0"/>

</feature>
